

Artem Furman

Web Developer

www.artemfurman.tech

Contact



+48 660 090 343



artemfurman@gmail.com



Poland

Languages

- **English**
- **Polish**
- Ukrainian
- Russian

Profile

Specializing in full-stack web application development, with a foundation in Python-backed machine learning and trading bot creation. Transitioning into front-end development, enriching a holistic approach to web applications. Drawn towards blockchain, notably NFTs for artists' independent distribution, with a wellengrained practice in AI.

Having a 12-year Music and Entertainment industry background, bringing a unique creative perspective to technical collaborations. Seeking a forward-thinking team dedicated to crafting meaningful, innovative solutions.

Education

2007 - 2010

Programming Faculty at the University of Information Technology and Management (TOP Programmers Program) in Rzeszów, Poland

2020 - 2021

Blockchain Course at the Ivan on Tech Academy

Work Experience

March 2022 - June 2022

Chatbot development at "Bielański Integrator Przedsiębiorczych" in Warsaw. Poland

April 2023 - present

Full-stack online store development in "Dobry Bartnik", remote

SRSS-A*

Tailwind CSS	
JavaScript/TypeScript	
React	
Next	
Node	
Python	
Django/REST	
PostgreSQL	
Solidity Smart Contracts	
Technical Analysis (Finance)	
Creative Ideation	

*Subjective Relative Skills Self-Assessment 69

